dailypicdump.com 2018-12-21

# Privacy Policy - DailyPicdump

**We take your privacy very seriously.**

* ###  Introduction

This privacy policy, which we adapted from a policy originally provided by [Automattic](http://www.automattic.com/), describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use our websites. Please read this notice very carefully.

* ###  Website Visitors

Like most website operators, DailyPicdump collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. DailyPicdump’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how DailyPicdump’s visitors use its website. From time to time, DailyPicdump may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

DailyPicdump also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. DailyPicdump does not use such information to identify its visitors, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

* ###  Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to DailyPicdump website choose to interact with DailyPicdump in ways that require DailyPicdump to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that DailyPicdump gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for DailyPicdump using facebook account to provide a email address. In each case, DailyPicdump collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with DailyPicdump does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

* ###  Cookies and Web Beacons

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. DailyPicdump uses cookies to help DailyPicdump identify and track visitors, their usage of DailyPicdump website, and their website access preferences. DailyPicdump visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using DailyPicdump’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of DailyPicdump’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

We do use cookies to store information, such as your session information, personal preferences when you visit our site. We also use third party advertisements on DailyPicdump website to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). See the Google Privacy Policy at <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html> for more information about data that may be collected, and what it might be used for. More information about using cookies: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site, Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet, Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

* ###  Links to Third Party Sites

This privacy policy only applies to information collected by DailyPicdump. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that DailyPicdump does not own or control, or employees that DailyPicdump does not manage. A DailyPicdump website may contain links to third party websites. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if any. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and DailyPicdump and its affiliates shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

* ###  Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, DailyPicdump may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in DailyPicdump’s sole discretion. DailyPicdump encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
